<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel id="1104">
    <display-name>Star Movies HD</display-name>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260623183000 +0530" stop="20260623185700 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Resident Evil: Afterlife</title>
    <desc>Alice learns of a mysterious haven named Arcadia while fighting the Umbrella Corporation. She decides to join a group of survivors headed to Arcadia, unaware that they are walking into a trap.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260623185700 +0530" stop="20260623203100 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Toy Story 3</title>
    <desc>With their beloved Andy preparing to leave for college, Woody (Tom Hanks), Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen), Jessie (Joan Cusack), and the rest of the toys find themselves headed for the attic but mistakenly wind up on the curb with the trash. Woody's quick thinking saves the gang, but all but Woody end up being donated to a day-care center. Unfortunately, the uncontrollable kids do not play nice, so Woody and the gang make plans for a great escape.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260623203100 +0530" stop="20260623211100 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Filler</title>
    <desc>Bringing the best in television.</desc>
    <category>Series</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260623211100 +0530" stop="20260623223000 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Detective Di Skeleton General</title>
    <desc>A village community is left reeling from the brutality of a series of mysterious killings, leading a renowned detective of the era to investigate in search of the truth.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260623223000 +0530" stop="20260623224900 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Filler</title>
    <desc>Bringing the best in television.</desc>
    <category>Series</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260623224900 +0530" stop="20260624002800 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Monster Hunt 2</title>
    <desc>After separating from his parents, Wuba, a monster, embarks on his own journey through the monster realm and teams up with a gambler to escape from the evil forces.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624002800 +0530" stop="20260624015200 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Zombie Shark</title>
    <desc>Four friends in a resort island have to save themselves from genetically modified sharks while trying to find a cure in a nearby research centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Movie</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624015200 +0530" stop="20260624031300 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>BraveStorm</title>
    <desc>Two families use giant robots to battle evil aliens.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624031300 +0530" stop="20260624044600 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>The Pacifier</title>
    <desc>Shane Wolfe, a Navy SEAL, fails to rescue a government scientist, Howard Plummer, from Serbian rebels. Later, he is assigned to protect Plummer's children from his enemies.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624044600 +0530" stop="20260624061800 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Alien vs. Predator</title>
    <desc>During their archaeological expedition on Bouvetøya Island in Antarctica, Weyland Industries and other scientists discover a buried pyramid. Soon they find themselves trapped in a war between two alien species.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624061800 +0530" stop="20260624075000 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>The Boss Baby</title>
    <desc>A new baby's arrival impacts a family, told from the point of view of a delightfully unreliable narrator, a wildly imaginative Seven year old named Tim. The most unusual Boss Baby arrives at Tim's home in a taxi, wearing a suit and carrying a briefcase. The instant sibling rivalry must soon be put aside when Tim discovers that Boss Baby is actually a spy on a secret mission, and only he can help thwart a dastardly plot that involves an epic battle between puppies and babies.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624075000 +0530" stop="20260624095600 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Black Widow</title>
    <desc>Natasha Romanoff, aka Black Widow, confronts the darker parts of her ledger when a dangerous conspiracy with ties to her past arises. Pursued by a force that will stop at nothing to bring her down, Natasha must deal with her history as a spy, and the broken relationships left in her wake long before she became an Avenger.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624095600 +0530" stop="20260624112600 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>The Dark Tower</title>
    <desc>Roland and the Man in Black share an ancient vendetta. They must fight to the death in an epic battle over the fate of the Universe.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624112600 +0530" stop="20260624130000 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Fantastic Four</title>
    <desc>Transported to an alternate universe, four young outsiders gain superhuman powers as they alter their physical form in shocking ways. Reed Richards becomes Mr. Fantastic, able to stretch and twist his body at will, while pal Ben Grimm gains immense strength as the Thing. Johnny Storm becomes the Human Torch, able to control and project fire, while his sister Sue becomes the Invisible Woman. Together, the team must harness their new abilities to prevent Doctor Doom from destroying the Earth.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624130000 +0530" stop="20260624151500 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>War for the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <desc>Caesar sets out to avenge the death of his wife and son after they are killed by rogue humans. However, his dark instincts begin to plague him on his journey.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624151500 +0530" stop="20260624164900 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Big Hero 6</title>
    <desc>A young robotics mastermind teams up with his brother's creation, a robot, to seek justice for his untimely death. Subsequently, they work together to face an unexpected threat.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260624164900 +0530" stop="20260624182959 +0530" channel="1104">
    <title>Free Guy</title>
    <desc>Guy lives a seemingly peaceful life as a bank teller. However, an encounter with a pretty but mysterious woman makes him realise that he is a non-playable character in a massive online video game.</desc>
    <category>Feature Film</category>
  </programme>
</tv>
